National Negro Opera Company Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Address Lists and Address Books, 1940-1961, (71 folders) (Box 30-35)
  - Address Lists, 1940-1961, undated (Box 30-32)
    - Washington, D.C. Women's Committee of the NNOC, undated (Box-folder 30/6)
    - Lists with designations, 1944-1961 and undated (Box-folder 30/7)
    - Lists without designations, 1944-1959 and undated (Box-folder 30/8)
    - Lists on slips of paper, undated (Box-folder 30/9)
    - Lists. Miscellaneous, 1943-1959 (Box-folder 30/10-12)
    - Card address file. Washington, D.C. mailing lists, undated (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Card address file. Washington, D.C. Mailing lists. Clubs and businesses, undated (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Card address file. Mailing lists - Unlabelled cards, undated (Box-folder 31/3-4)
    - Card address file. Mailing lists - loose cards, undated (Box-folder 31/5-6)
    - Mailing list. Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, undated (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Mailing list. Washington, D.C., undated (Box-folder 32/2)
    - List of ministers and churches, undated, Page one is missing. (Box-folder 32/3)
    - Campaign minutes and kits, undated (Box-folder 32/4)
    - List of opera producing organizations in the United States, September 1957 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - List of opera groups presenting operatic stage performances in the USA between October 15, 1956 and September 15, 1957, 1957 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - Lists - with designations, undated (Box-folder 32/7)
    - Lists - without designations, undated (Box-folder 32/8)
    - Lists - miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 32/9)
  - Address Books, 1942-1959, undated (Box 32-35)
    - Membership enrollment of the Washington Guild (and other associated guilds) of the NNOC, undated (Box-folder 32/10)
    - Pittsburgh, Pa. addresses and other mailing lists, undated (Box-folder 32/11)
    - Unidentified address book, undated (Box-folder 32/12)
    - Chicago Board of Governors/Chicago talent, undated (Box-folder 33/1)
    - New York Chorus members. Contact information, undated (Box-folder 33/2)
    - New York Guild, NNOC addresses, undated, Address book is labelled "recent mailing list." (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Pittsburgh, Pa. chorus and committees; Washington, D.C. mailing list, undated (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Washington Youth Guild members and officials, undated (Box-folder 33/5)
    - Addresses of Guild members, undated (Box-folder 33/6)
    - Notebook: New talent, old talent and contestants, undated, Addresses and contacts contained in a Juniata Composition notebook. (Box-folder 33/7)
    - Untitled contact/address notebook, undated, Addresses and contacts contained in a Royal Composition notebook. (Box-folder 33/8)
    - Names and addresses, undated, Names and addresses contained in a composition notebook. (Box-folder 33/9)
    - Addresses and names, undated, Addresses and names contained in a small hardbound blue book. (Box-folder 33/10)
    - Telephone index, undated, Addresses and names contained in an unbound booklet. (Box-folder 33/11)
    - Address book (blue), undated (Box-folder 34/1)
    - Addresses - tan note pad, undated (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Registration book - NNOC, undated (Box-folder 34/3)
    - Vocalists address book, undated, Red address book that lists vocalists by vocal type. (Box-folder 34/4)
    - Vocalists address book, undated, Red address book that lists vocalists by vocal type. (Box-folder 34/4)
    - Opera - address book, undated (Box-folder 34/5)
    - Chicago talent and music lovers address book, undated (Box-folder 34/6)
    - Pittsburgh and McKeesport addresses, undated (Box-folder 34/7)
    - Washington, D.C. address books (3 books), circa 1959 (Box-folder 34/8)
    - Boston, Detroit, New York and Pittsburgh addresses, undated (Box-folder 34/9)
    - Address and phone book, undated (Box-folder 34/10)
    - Rite-form account book (unbound), circa 1957 (Box-folder 34/11)
    - Telephone index (unbound), undated (Box-folder 34/12)
    - Addresses/telephone numbers (unbound), undated (Box-folder 34/13)
    - The Ordering of Moses (1959 production) Addresses, 1959 (Box-folder 35/1)
    - Small black address book, undated (Box-folder 35/2)
    - The Ordering of Moses Addresses/contacts, 1957, Cover title: Dancers. (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Address/telephone book (green cloth bound), undated (Box-folder 35/4)
    - Address notepad, 1942 (Box-folder 35/5)
    - Address/accounts notebook, undated (Box-folder 35/6)
    - Addresses (small green notebook), undated (Box-folder 35/7)
    - Unbound notepad, 1943 (Box-folder 35/8)
    - Rehearsal notepad pages, 1946 (Box-folder 35/9)
    - Addresses and accounts notebook, undated (Box-folder 35/10)
    - La Traviata (1943 production) addresses, 1943 (Box-folder 35/11)
    - Addresses, undated (Box-folder 35/12)
    - Addresses - New York City, undated (Box-folder 35/13)
    - Addresses - several cities/Guilds (bound book), undated (Box-folder 35/14)
    - Addresses (loose pages A-Z) - various cities, undated (Box-folder 35/15)
    - Addresses (loose pages A-Z), undated (Box-folder 35/16)
    - Washington, D.C. addresses (loose pages), 1943 (Box-folder 35/17)
- Notebooks, 1932-1961, (70 folders) (Box 36-40)
  Notebooks (disassembled and intact) containing specific subject content, secretarial and stenographer notes, or other general notes that highlight the daily office operations of the National Negro Opera Company and related organizations in which Mary Cardwell Dawson was involved.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Appointments, receipts and expenses, undated (Box-folder 36/1)
  - Cash flow records and payments, 1956 (Box-folder 36/2)
  - Checkbook number 1, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 40/3)
  - Checkbook number 2, 1958-1961 (Box-folder 40/4)
  - Chorus members addresses, undated (Box-folder 36/3)
  - Draft letters, undated (Box-folder 36/4)
  - Draft letters, 1956 (Box-folder 36/5)
  - Draft letters (spiral stenographic notebook), undated (Box-folder 36/6)
  - Draft letters; sponsor lists; notes from meetings (stenographic notebook), undated (Box-folder 36/7)
  - Expense records. Black S.E. ledger, 1941 (Box-folder 36/8)
  - Expense records. Gray S.E. ledger, 1942 (Box-folder 36/9)
  - Expense records. Miscellaneous (brown marbled notebook), 1948 (Box-folder 36/10)
  - Expense records. Miscellaneous (brown spiral notebook), 1947, 1949 (Box-folder 36/11)
  - Financial ledger, 1943 (Box-folder 36/12)
  - Financial ledger, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 36/13)
  - Leave records. (green cloth notebook), 1943 (Box-folder 36/14)
  - Members of the Development Committee. Address list, undated (Box-folder 36/15)
  - Membership fees notebook, 1954 (Box-folder 40/6)
  - Membership list, receipts/disbursements and a dinner report, 1939-1940; 1951, Notebook includes a membership list (page 4); receipts and disbursements accounts (page 50); and a dinner report from 1951 (page 14). (Box-folder 40/7)
  - Membership lists and financial records, 1949 (Box-folder 40/8)
  - Money receipt books (4), 1944, 1950, 1955 and 1959-1961 (Box-folder 36/16)
  - Music notebook, undated (Box-folder 37/1)
  - Notebook. Addresses, undated (Box-folder 37/2)
  - Notebook. Assignments (B. Edwards), undated (Box-folder 37/3)
  - Notebook. Cash accounts ledger, 1947 (Box-folder 40/2)
  - Notebook. NNOC Campaign Fund, 1960 (Box-folder 40/1)
  - Notebook. National Negro Opera Company Foundation (Barbara Edwards' notebook), undated, Notebook belonging to Barbara Edwards. (Box-folder 37/4)
  - Notebook. Notes by Barbara Edwards, June 20, 1950 (Box-folder 37/5)
  - Notebook. Miscellaneous notes, 1932 (Box-folder 40/9)
  - Notebook. Miscellaneous, including poem Opportunity, undated (Box-folder 37/6)
  - Notebook. Scripture notes, June 20, 1950 (Box-folder 37/7)
  - Notebook. Big 25 composition - Miscellaneous notes, 1955 (Box-folder 37/8)
  - Notebook. Black composition book - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box-folder 37/9)
  - Notebook. Improved compact binder - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box-folder 37/10)
  - Notebook. Premier composition binder - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box-folder 37/11)
  - Notebook. Riteform binder - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box-folder 37/12)
  - Notebook. Spiral composition binder - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box-folder 37/13)
  - Notebook. unbound pages - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box-folder 37/14)
  - Notebook. Bound notebook (cover missing) - Miscellaneous notes, 1941 (Box-folder 37/15)
  - Notebook. unbound pages - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box-folder 37/16)
  - Notebook. unbound pages - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box-folder 37/17)
  - Notebook. Aida notes (Weekly time book), undated (Box-folder 37/18)
  - Notebooks (2). Ouanga expenses, 1956 (Box-folder 38/1)
  - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania mailing list, 1940s (Box-folder 38/2)
  - Receipts book, 1953, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 40/10)
  - Records. City vocal contest, Salem Methodist Church, 1945 (Box-folder 38/3)
  - Report for cash. Ledger, 1945 (Box-folder 38/4)
  - Secretarial notebook. Ledger, undated, Notebook belonging to Juanita Walker. (Box-folder 38/5)
  - Secretarial notebooks. Draft letters and lists, undated (Box-folder 38/6)
  - Secretarial notebooks. Shorthand, undated (Box-folder 38/7-11)
  - Secretarial notebooks (3). Shorthand exercises, undated (Box-folder 38/12-14)
  - Small blue notebook. Miscellaneous contact data, undated (Box-folder 39/1)
  - Stenographer's notebook, 1950, Notebook belonging to Rita Maria Carrington. (Box-folder 39/2)
  - Telephone directories (4), undated (Box-folder 39/3)
  - Telephone log, 1956 (Box-folder 39/4)
  - Telephone log, undated (Box-folder 39/5)
  - Telephone log and miscellaneous notes, undated (Box-folder 39/6)
  - Ticket accounts (book), 1944 (Box-folder 39/7)
  - Ticket accounts (book), 1948 (Box-folder 39/8)
  - Ticket orders (book), undated (Box-folder 39/9)
  - Ticket orders to fill - opera, undated (Box-folder 39/10)
  - Ticket report notebook, 1933 (Box-folder 39/11)
  - Ticket report notebook. Madison Square Garden members report, 1934 (Box-folder 40/5)
  - Ticket sales notebooks, 1943, 1948 and 1951 (Box-folder 39/12)
- Music, 1879-1961, (15 folders) (Box 41-43)
  Includes manuscripts, printed music, script fragments and synopses.
  Arranged alphabetically by composer.
  - Andrews, Ismay. Tradition; song for mixed voices. New York: Handy Brothers Music Co., 1946., Printed score; 16 p.; Words and music by Ismay Andrews.; Four copies. (Box-folder 41/1)
  - Aylward, Florence. Beloved, it is morn; for voice and organ/piano. New York: Chappell & Co., 1896., Printed score; 3 p.; Words by Emily Hickey; music by Florence Aylward. (Box-folder 41/1)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian. Bist du bei mir; for voice and piano. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1943., Printed score; 5 p.; Music by J. S. Bach; piano accompaniment by Carl Deis.; Original German text anonymous. Translation and sacred text by Margaret Bristol. (Box-folder 41/1)
  - Berlin, Irving. God bless America; arranged for mixed voices and piano. New York: Irving Berlin, Inc., 1939., Printed score; 7 p.; Words and music by Irving Berlin; arranged for mixed voices by Charles Boutelle. (Box-folder 41/1)
  - Bischoff, J. W. The Summer wind; for voice and piano. Boston: Arthur P. Schmidt Co., 1906., Printed score; 7 p.; Music by J. W. Bischoff; words by Walter Learned. (Box-folder 41/1)
  - Bizet, Georges. Carmen; opera in four acts. Boston: C. C. Birchard & Company, 1927., Printed score (Chorus parts only); 53 p.; Music by Georges Bizet; original text by H. Meilhac and L. Halevy; English words by Sybil Paget and J. Lilian Vandevere.; Three copies. (Box-folder 41/2)
  - Buck, Dudley. Golden legend. My Redeemer and my Lord, Scene V; for voice and piano. Cincinnati: John Church Company, 1908., Printed score; 9 p.; Music by Dudley Buck; text taken from a poem by Henry Wadsworth Longfellow. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Burleigh, H. T. Little David, play on your harp; negro spiritual, arranged for voice and piano. New York: G. Ricordi & Co., 1921., Printed score; 6 p.; Arranged by H. T. Burleigh. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Burleigh, H. T. Little mother of mine; for voice and piano. New York: G. Ricordi & Co., 1917., Printed score; 6 p. (incomplete, pages missing); Music by H. T. Burleigh; words by Walter H. Brown. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Burleigh, H. T. Sinner. Please doan let dis harves' pass; negro spiritual, arranged for voice and piano. New York: G. Ricordi & Co., 1917., Printed score; 5 p.; Arranged by H. T. Burleigh. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Cain, Noble. The King of love my shepherd is; anthem arranged for two choirs (SATB) and piano. New York: Harold Flammer Publisher, Inc., 1948., Printed score; 10 p.; Adapted from an ancient Irish melody by Noble Cain; psalm as verse by Henry W. Baker. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Cain, Noble. O Lord, don't turn away; for chorus (SATB), A Cappella and rehearsal piano accompaniment. [S.l.: Choral Press, Inc.], 1961., Printed score; 10 p.; Music by Noble Dain; words by Philip Maxwell. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Campbell, Lucie E. Jesus give me water; for solo voice, chorus and piano. Nashville, Tennessee: E. W. D. Isaac, 1946., Printed score; 5 p.; Words and music by Lucie E. Campbell. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Campbell-Tipton, Louis. A Spirit flower song; for four-part chorus (mixed voices) and piano. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1936., Printed score; 7 p.; Music by Louis Campbell-Tipton; words by B. Martin Stanton.; Arrangement by Wallingford Riegger.; Two copies. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Chambers, Lucille Cundiff. Chanson sans paroles, opus 18; for piano solo., Manuscript piano score; 4 p.; Dedicated to Mary Cardwell Dawson by the composer. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Coenen, Willem. Frühlingslied =Lovely spring; song for voice and piano. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., [19--], Printed score; 7 p.; Words and music by Willem Coenen. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Cooper, Esther. Negro sketches. Lord, hold our Your hand to me; for voice and piano. Pittsburgh: Volkwein Brothers, Inc., 1947., Printed score; 5 p.; Music by Esther Cooper; words by Helen Williams. (Box-folder 41/3)
  - Densmore, John H. A Spring fancy; for voice and piano. Boston: Oliver Ditson Company, 1920., Printed score; 7 p.; Music by John H. Densmore; words by Mary Gardenia. (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Dett, R. Nathaniel. The Dett collection of negro spirituals; second group. Chicago: Hall & McCreary Company, 1936., Printed score (vocal parts with piano); 32 p.; Includes originals, settings, anthems and motets, with an essay (by Dett) "Understanding the negro spiritual."; The H. & M. Auditorium Series no. 14. (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Dett, R. Nathaniel. The Dett collection of negro spirituals; third group. Chicago: Hall & McCreary Company, 1936., Printed score (vocal parts with piano); 32 p.; Includes originals, settings, anthems and motets, with an essay (by Dett) "The Authenticity of the spiritual."; The H. & M. Auditorium Series no. 15. (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Dett, R. Nathaniel. The Ordering of Moses; Biblical folk scene for soli, chorus and orchestra. Melville, New York: J. Fischer & Bro., 1965., Printed piano-vocal score; 123 p.; Text based on Scripture and folk lore, compiled and set to music by R. Nathaniel Nett. (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Dett, R. Nathaniel. The Ordering of Moses. O Hear me Lord; an added tenor aria for the Prayer Scene of Act II., Manuscript piano-vocal score (vocal part with piano); 4 p.; Additional tenor aria, arranged by Roy O'Loughlin, music taken from the Prelude music of the first act of The Ordering of Moses; words are from the Bible, Exodus, Chapter 5.; Includes a one-page letter by Roy O'Laughlin to Mrs. Dawson, dated March 6, 1960, in which he discusses this added aria. (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Diton, Cairnetta B. Nanm's going onward; for voice and piano. New York: Cairnetta B. Diton, 1959., Printed score; 3 p.; Words and music by Cairnetta B. Diton; vocal arrangement by Carl Diton. (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Dorsey, Thomas A. Our Father who art in Heaven - The Lord's prayer; for voice and piano. Chicago: Thomas A. Dorsey, 1940., Printed score; 4 p.; Music by Thomas A. Dorsey; vocal text from the Bible.; Two copies. (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Duparc, Henri. Phidylé; for voice and piano. Boston: Boston Music Company, 1915., Printed score; 13 p.; Music by Henri Duparc; original text (French) by Leconte de Lisle, with English words by M. Louise Baum. (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Dupree, Reese. Shortnin' bread; for voice and piano. New York: Clarence Williams Publishing Co., Inc., 1938., Printed score; 13 p.; Words and music by Reese Dupree; arranged by Clarence Williams. (Box-folder 41/4)
  - Evanti, Lillian. Forward march to victory; voice and piano. Washington, D.C.: Lillian Evanti, 1943., Printed score; 3 p. (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Evanti, Lillian. Twenty-Third Psalm; for mixed quartette and piano. New York: Handy Brothers Music Co., 1942., Printed score; 10 p.; Arranged by Charles L. Cooke.; Inscribed to Mary Cardwell Dawson by the composer. (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Fauré, Gabriel. Impromptu, no. 2 in F minor, opus 31; for piano. Boston: Boston Music Co., 1910., Printed score; 11 p. (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Fax, Mark. Rally song; vocals with piano., Manuscript score (photocopy); 1 p. (Box-folder 41/5)
    Song written for the NNOC Foundation's 1953 drive for public support. Song was donated to this cause by the composer.
    Two copies.
  - Flégier, Ange. Le Cor = The Horn; for voice and piano. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1898., Printed score; 7 p.; Words and music by Ange Flégier.; English version by Isabella G. Parker. (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Gounod, Charles. Ave Maria; for violin or violoncello and harmonium. [S.l.: s.n.], [19--], Printed score; 7 p. (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Gounod, Charles. Faust; lyric drama in 4 acts. Chorus score. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1930., Printed score; 59 p. (Box-folder 41/5)
  - Hageman, Richard. Do not go, my love; for voice and piano. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1945., Printed score; 5 p.; Music by Richard Hageman; words by Sir Rabindranath Tagore. (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Handel, George Frideric. Messiah. I know that my Redeemer liveth; for voice and piano. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., [n.d.], Printed score; 7 p.; Music by Handel; text: Job 19:25-26; I Corinthians 15:20. (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Handy, William Christopher. Opportunity; for voice (Medium) and piano. New York: W. C. Handy Music Publisher, 1934., Printed score; 5 p.; Music by W. C. Handy; poem by Walter Malone.; Autographed by the composer. (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Hardelot, Guy, d'. Because; for voice and piano. New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1902., Printed score; 7 p.; Music by Guy d'Hardelot; words by Edward Teschemacher. (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Herbert, Victor. Naughty Marietta. Italian street song; for four-part chorus (mixed voices), soprano solo and piano. New York: M. Witmark & Sons, 1915., Printed score; 13 p.; Music by Victor Herbert; lyric by Rida Johnson-Young.; Arranged by the composer.; Two copies. (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Hill, Alexander. A Song (How the first song was born); for voice and piano. New York: Handy Brothers Music Co., Inc., 1934., Printed score; 5 p.; Words and music by Alexander Hill. (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Ilgenfritz, McNair. As we part; for voice and piano. New York: Edward Schuberth & Co., [n.d.], Printed score (music missing, cover only); Music by McNair Ilgenfritz; words by Frederick Peterson. (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Jackson, Mary C. Soft winds; for voice and piano. Pittsburgh: Volkwein Brothers, Inc., 1939., Printed score (music missing, cover only); Words and music by Mary C. Jackson. (Box-folder 41/6)
  - Jaime, Benjamin Francisco H. (The Afro-American) Te Deum in C, opus 15; chorus (mixed voices), trumpet, organ and piano., Manuscript piano-vocal score (photocopy); 95 p.; Music by Benjamin H. Francisco Jaime; text attributed to St. Ambrose of Milan.; Dedicated to the National Negro Opera Foundation, Inc.; Two copies. (Box-folder 42/1)
  - Jaime, Benjamin Francisco H. An Alto rhapsody on Psalm 130, opus 24; chorus for womens' voices (with optional tenors) and piano., Manuscript piano-vocal score (photocopy); 8 p.; Music by Benjamin H. Francisco Jaime; text: the Old Testament, Book of Psalms.; Composed during October 1960. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Jaime, Benjamin Francisco H. How do I love thee?, opus 25; for medium voice and piano., Manuscript piano-vocal score (photocopy); 4 p.; Music by Benjamin Francisco Jaime; words by Elizabeth Barrett Browning.; Composed during November 14-24, 1960.; Commissioned by Mr. and Mrs. (Virginia) Walker, Hurley, New Mexico. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Jaime, Benjamin Francisco H. The Lord's Prayer, fourth setting, opus 26; for bass voice and piano., Manuscript piano-vocal score (photocopy); 4 p.; Music by Benjamin H. Francisco Jaime; text: the Bible. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Jaime, Benjamin Francisco H.. Prayer, opus 7; musical setting of The Lord's Prayer, for bass, chorus and piano. [S.l.]: Benj. Francisco Jaime, 1952., Printed piano-vocal score; 10 p.; Composed during September 1952. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Jessye, Eva. Awake! Arise! Ascend! Hymn to womanhood; vocals with melodic accompaniment., Manuscript score (photocopy); 1 p. (Box-folder 42/2)
    Words and music by Eva Jessye.
    Song written for the National Association of Colored Women's Clubs, Inc. Song was introduced at the biennial session, New York Convention, 1960 by Dr. Rosa L. Gragg, National President.
    Seven copies.
  - Johnson, Hall, arranger. City called Heaven; negro spiritual, for voice and piano. New York: Robbins Music Corporation, 1930., Printed score; 6 p. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Johnson, Herbert. Face to face; sacred song for voice and piano. Boston: Boston Music Company, 1938., Printed score; 5 p. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Lasso, Orlando di. Echo song; for three-part double chorus of women's voices and piano. New York: Harold Flammer Publisher, Inc., 1937., Printed score; 7 p. (Box-folder 42/2)
    Music by Orlando di Lasso; English version by Alfred Marlhom.
    Arranged by Gerald Wilfring Gore.
  - Leoni, Franco. The Birth of morn; song for voice and piano. New York: Chappell & Co., Inc., 1902., Printed score; 3 p.; Music by Franco Leoni; words by Paul Laurence Dunbar. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Lincke, Paul. The Glow Worm = Glühwürmchen. Idyl; for piano solo. New York: Edward B. Marks Music Corporation, 1930., Printed score; 7 p. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Liszt, Franz. Liebestraum = Dream of love; song for voice and piano. Chicago: Forster Music Publisher, Inc., 1925., Printed score; 9 p.; Arrangement by Tito Schipa.; Edited by Maurice Rosenfeld.; English version by Lawrence Lipton. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Manney, Charles Fonteyn. Jeunesse, valse de ballet; for piano. Boston: Oliver Ditson Company, 1927., Printed score; 5 p. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - McClennan, Walter N. Love me and I'll be satisfied; song for voice and piano. Washington, D.C.: Walter N. McClennan, 1938., Printed score; 4 p.; Words and music by Walter N. McClennan.; Autographed by the composer. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Offenbach, Jacques. Les Contes d'Hoffman. O Lovely night barcarolle; for four-part chorus (mixed voices) and piano. New York: G. Schirmer, Inc., 1910., Printed score; 7 p.; Music by Jacques Offenbach; English version by Louise Baum.; Arranged by Max Spicker. (Box-folder 42/2)
  - Ponce, Manuel M. Little star; song for voice (high) and piano. New York: G. Ricordi & Co., Inc., 1923., Printed piano-vocal score and vocal part; 4 p.; Music by Manuel M. Ponce; arranged and translated by Frank La Forge. (Box-folder 42/3)
  - Ponchielli, Amilcare. La Gioconda. Cielo e mar = Lo! sky and sea; aria for voice (low) and piano. New York: Carl Fischer, Inc., 1927., Printed piano-vocal score; 8 p.; Music by Amilcare Ponchielli; text by Tobia Gorrio, with English translation by Margaret Churchill.; Edited by N. Clifford Page. (Box-folder 42/3)